# STELIOS KOUROUPAS

Phone: (347) 337-7349 | Email: Redbow237@gmail.com | City: Plymouth, MN 55411

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/stylianos-kouroupas-905512183/

Github: https://github.com/Steliosk9 Portfolio: https://steliosk9.github.io/My\_Portofolio\_Site/

#### **SUMMARY**

Junior web developer with a stellar customer service record and outstanding work ethic. For the last 2 years i worked in several projects building Front & back end applications Using multiple technologies and languages like JavaScript, Java, React, Node, MongoDB, SQL etc. Passionate about approaching programming challenges from different angles and collaborating with others to create meaningful web applications.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JavaScript, Java, JQuery, ReactJs, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, MySQL, Ajax, MVC, Restful API, Handlebars, Sequelize, XML, Firebase, Bootstrap, Material-UI, Microsoft office, VSCode Adobe Photoshop Elements.

### **PROJECTS**

### **Google Books Search**

https://github.com/Steliosk9/-React-Google-Books | <a href="https://google-books-78.herokuapp.com/">https://google-books-78.herokuapp.com/</a>
Summary: A React-based Google Books Search app utilizes React life-cycle methods to query and display books based on user searches, and uses Node, Express and MongoDB (MERN) so that users can save books to review or purchase later.

# **React-Clicky-Game**

https://github.com/Steliosk9/React-Clicky-Game | <a href="https://stormy-earth-37478.herokuapp.com/">https://github.com/Steliosk9/React-Clicky-Game | <a href="https://stormy-earth-37478.herokuapp.com/">https://stormy-earth-37478.herokuapp.com/</a>
Summary: Memory game built with **React** & **Bootstrap.** Click on each character once to win the game. Click on a character twice, and it's game over for you!

### **Eat-Da-Burger**

https://github.com/Steliosk9/React-Clicky-Game | <a href="https://burger-sequelizer.herokuapp.com/burgers/">https://burger-sequelizer.herokuapp.com/burgers/</a>
Summary: A Node, Express, Handlebars, and MySQL burger app that lets users input the names of burgers they'd like to eat... and then devour them!

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Freelancer Web Developer, - Minneapolis, MN - Sep 2019 – Today

- Meeting with new prospective clients to review website specifications
- Designing, coding new Websites using Multiple technologies and databases .
- Maintain existing Websites .

# Sales Accociate "Avis Budget Group" - Minneapolis, MN - July 2018 - Today

- Process transactions of vehicle rental and processing payments
- Provide options for insurance coverage for any type of protection related to the vehicle.
- Upgading to a bigger or better vehicle base the the customer needs .

# Sales Asssosiate "Mazda of North Miami" - May 2017 - May 2018

- Established relationships with new customers .
- Showed customers how to use acquired vehicles after delivery.
- Maintained contact with existing customers through meeting, emails and by phone.

### Sales Accosiate 'Pompia inc' - Fort Lauderdale, FL - Sep 2015 - May 2017

- Expanded existing business base by resolving customer concerns .
- Adopted marketing strategies to conduct sales programs.
- Attended all food shows and events related to industry.

### General Manager at 'Food and Trade' - Mykonos, Greece - Mar 2013 - July 2015

- Nurtured business relationships with Food service accounts and handled distributors .
- Extended desired information to customers as well as managed plans and objectives, meeting territory budget.
- Coordinated with all support staff.

## Sales Coordinator 'Red Bull' Athens, Greece- Aug 2010 - Oct 2012

- Actively supported company sales team .
- Coordinated sales details, pre-sale material and after-sale deliveries.
- Participated in execution of sales strategies

### Food Sales Representative 'Coca Cola' Company - Athens, Greece - June 2007 - July 2010

- Nurtured trusting relationships.
- Received all sort of payments, orders and invoicing.
- Maintained sales records, reviewed sales prices.

#### ACCOMPLISHMENTS

**Food & Trade** – Top seller of the year in the region for opening 125 new customers in (2) months.

**Red Bull** – One of the top Three person in the Region for selling our product.

**Coca Cola Co** - Exceeded Sales Associate goals by 25% on a quarterly basis. Promoted to leader of my team.

**Avis & Budget Group** – Top 3 in sales for the last 18 months in the Minneapolis Area.

**Mazda of 'North Miami** – salesman of the month December 2017.

### **EDUCATION**

• University of Minnesota "Full Stack Wed Developer Boot Camp" A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, iQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars & ReactJS, React (MERN).

• High school diploma.